Raffles have not lost their relevance in the world of sales.
We all remember the classic slips of paper we were given in
school to determine who was going to speak first or who was going
to choose the most talented ball player during physical education class.
The origin of raffles dates back to the Renaissance,
with Francis I,
French monarch,
who launched a very unusual competition in those years,
called Blanc,
and used it to pay the costs of the continuous wars of the time.
Raffles,
over the years and with the arrival of new technologies,
have been improving and becoming more attractive on a professional level,
especially because they are a tactic that does
not require a very strong investment to sell more,
get the attention of new buyers and retain those you already have.
So far everything sounds incredible,
but be careful,
without a clear plan,
this activity can become a nightmare for you.
There will always be those who are dissatisfied who will think that Juan
Pérez did not have to win or that he did it because he was someone's friend.
To avoid this,
you must be clear about the process of selecting the winner,
have the necessary tools to complete each activity with ease,
and share with participants all the
bases that will be used to select the winner.